Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.3.6
Marist College
  Box 1537 - Box 1540
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1541 - Box 1544
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1545 - Box 1548
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1549
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Martin and Osa Johnson, undated; 1 (Box 1549)
    - Martin Johnson and Osa, 1
    - Verso: Martin Johnson and Osa, 1-verso
    - Holding The Explorers Club flag; on the ball field, 2
    - Note: Holding The Explorers Club flag; on the ball field, 3
    - Note: Martin + Osa Johnson friends of LT's; Osa Johnson wrote book called "I married adventure", 4
  - Subject files: Loren R. Johnson, 1937 November; 2 (Box 1549)
    - Near Red Sulphur Springs, 1
    - Verso: Near Red Sulphur Springs, 1-verso
    - His black Majesty "Buddy", 2
    - Verso: His black Majesty "Buddy", 2-verso
    - [illegible] toward [illegible], 3
    - Verso: [illegible] toward [illegible], 3-verso
    - Near Salt Sulpher Springs, 4
    - Verso: Near Salt Sulpher Springs, 4-verso
  - Subject files: Duke Kahanamoku [color photographs], undated; 3 (Box 1549)
    - Tit for tat! This is a not-so-hot shot taken recently - hope you'll like it regardless! Nadine and Duke Kahanamoku; Honolulu 1950, 1
    - Verso: Tit for tat! This is a not-so-hot shot taken recently - hope you'll like it regardless! Nadine and Duke Kahanamoku; Honolulu 1950, 1-verso
    - Note: [letter from Nadine and Duke Kahanamoku to Lowell Thomas concerning photograph 3.1], [PDF], 2
    - Duke Kahanamoku, LT, Gene Tunney; 50th anniversary party at [Thornburg?], 3
    - Verso: Duke Kahanamoku, LT, Gene Tunney; 50th anniversary party at [Thornburg?], 3-verso
    - Duke Kahanamoku, LT, Gene Tunney; 50th anniversary party at [Thornburg?], 4
  - Subject files: Dorothy Killgallen, undated; 4 (Box 1549)
    - Photo shows - Mr. Robert M. Catharine, President of the Dollar Savings Bank, with Miss Dorothy Kilgallen, TV star and columnist, who holds the winning doll, made by Mrs. Edward J. Gilligan, in the Bank's Annual Gift Doll Dressing Contest, 1
    - Note: Photo shows - Mr. Robert M. Catharine, President of the Dollar Savings Bank, with Miss Dorothy Kilgallen, TV star and columnist, who holds the winning doll, made by Mrs. Edward J. Gilligan, in the Bank's Annual Gift Doll Dressing Contest, 2
  - Subject files: Fumitaka Konoye, 1937 June 15; 5 (Box 1549)
    - Caption: To that Great Adventurer Lowell Thomas in happy remembrance of my first adventure before a microphone on his program. June 15, 1937 [signed] Fumitaka Konoye, 1
  - Subject files: Kuwait, 1969 October; 6 (Box 1549)
    - Isa K. Sabbagh, Pub. Affairs Officer, U.S. Embassy, Kuwait and Ambassador John Walsh, 1
    - Isa K. Sabbagh, Pub. Affairs Officer, U.S. Embassy, Kuwait and Ambassador John Walsh, 2
    - Isa K. Sabbagh, Pub. Affairs Officer, U.S. Embassy, Kuwait and Ambassador John Walsh, 3
    - Isa K. Sabbagh, Pub. Affairs Officer, U.S. Embassy, Kuwait and Ambassador John Walsh, 4
    - Verso: Isa K. Sabbagh, Pub. Affairs Officer, U.S. Embassy, Kuwait and Ambassador John Walsh, 4-verso
    - Caption: To Lowell, with admiration, John P. Walsh; Kuwait, October 1969; [Lowell Thomas and Ambassador John Walsh], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and John P. Walsh], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and John P. Walsh], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and John P. Walsh], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and John P. Walsh], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and John P. Walsh], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and Isa K. Sabbagh], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas and Isa K. Sabbagh], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and Isa K. Sabbagh], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas and Isa K. Sabbagh], 14
  - Subject files: Lake Placid, circa 1930s - 1958; 7 (Box 1549)
    - Walter O'Keefe [right, Lowell Thomas, center] [Winter Sports Carnival at Lake Placid], 1
    - Verso: Walter O'Keefe [right, Lowell Thomas, center] [Winter Sports Carnival at Lake Placid], 1-verso
    - [Walter O'Keefe right, Lowell Thomas, left] [Winter Sports Carnival at Lake Placid], 2
    - [Walter O'Keefe right, Lowell Thomas, left] [Winter Sports Carnival at Lake Placid], 3
    - [Walter O'Keefe left, Lowell Thomas, right] [Winter Sports Carnival at Lake Placid], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and unidentified woman], 5
    - Lake Placid Club January 1958, 6
    - Verso: Lake Placid Club January 1958, 6-verso
    - Lake Placid Club January 1958, 7
    - Verso: Lake Placid Club January 1958, 7-verso
  - Subject files: Thomas LaMonte, undated; 8 (Box 1549)
    - Thomas LaMonte, 1
    - Note: Thomas LaMonte, 2
  - Subject files: Ralph Conover Lankler, undated; 9 (Box 1549)
    - [Ralph Conover Lankler], 1
  - Subject files: Laplanders, undated; 10 (Box 1549)
    - [Laplanders], 1
  - Subject files: D. H. Lawrence [portrait by Mary K. Jones], 1929; 11 (Box 1549)
    - Portrait D. H. Lawrence by May Klauder Jones 1929, 1
    - Verso: Portrait D. H. Lawrence by May Klauder Jones 1929, 1-verso
  - Subject files: T. E. Lawrence [photographs for use in Lawrence of Arabia: The Man and the Motive by Anthony Nutting], 1961; 12 (Box 1549)
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Paul D. Burns, Production Manager of Anthony Nutting's book on T. E. Lawrence concerning reproduction rights to photographs], 1
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 2
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 3
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 4
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 5
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 6
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 7
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 8
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], [one sheet contains 12.9 & 12.10], 9
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], [one sheet contains 12.9 & 12.10], 10
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 11
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], [one sheet contains 12.12 & 12.13], 12
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], [one sheet contains 12.12 & 12.13], 13
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], [one sheet contains 12.14 & 12.15], 14
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], [one sheet contains 12.14 & 12.15], 15
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 16
    - [photographs of T.E. Lawrence and Arabia Campaign of First World War], 17
  - Subject files: T. E. Lawrence [portrait by Erik Kennington], 1943; 13 (Box 1549)
    - [portrait by Erik Kennington], 1
    - Verso: T. E. Lawrence by Erik Kennington presented to Colonel Charles Sweeny by the artist. Church Fenton Yorkshire, September 14, 1943., 1-verso
  - Subject files: Leather trunk series (Frances Ryan [Thomas]), 1915 - 1916; 14 (Box 1549)
    - [France Ryan (Thomas)], 1
    - [France Ryan (Thomas)], 2
    - [France Ryan (Thomas)], 3
  - Subject files: Leather trunk series (Virginia), circa 1915 - 1916; 15 (Box 1549)
    - Miss Elizabeth Worsley, Leesburg, Va. [Virginia], 1
    - Verso: Miss Elizabeth Worsley, Leesburg, Va. [Virginia], 1-verso
    - [Man and a woman standing on a front porch (Virginia)], 2
    - [Statue outside of a building in Virginia], 3
    - [A house in Virginia], 4
    - [Men cutting up logs in Virginia], 5
    - [Men on an ox cart in Virginia], 6
    - [City street in Virginia], 7
  - Subject files: Leather trunk series (President Woodrow Wilson at Princeton), circa 1914 - 1916; 16 (Box 1549)
    - [President Woodrow Wilson], 1
    - [President Woodrow Wilson with a crowd of people], 2
  - Subject files: Mabel Barbee Lee, undated; 17 (Box 1549)
    - [Mabel Barbee Lee], 1
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Mabel Barbee Lee], 2
  - Subject files: World Champion Liar, circa 1930s; 18 (Box 1549)
    - Wold [sic] Champ Liar, L.T. - Prosper Buranelli L.T.J. [World Champion Liar, Lowell Thomas, Prosper Buranelli, Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 1
    - Verso: Wold [sic] Champ Liar, L.T. - Prosper Buranelli L.T.J. [World Champion Liar, Lowell Thomas, Prosper Buranelli, Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 1-verso
  - Subject file: Charles A. Lindbergh [50th anniversary celebration], 1977; 19 (Box 1549)
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from James A. Kennedy, Director of Public Relations, United Airlines, concerning photographs], 1
    - Tom Blumenthal with commemorative book on Lindbergh, 2
    - Verso: Tom Blumenthal with commemorative book on Lindbergh, 2-verso
    - Tom Blumenthal and General Jimmy Doolittle, 3
    - Verso: Tom Blumenthal and General Jimmy Doolittle, 3-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Richard J. Ferris (Pres. Of United Airlines), 4
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Richard J. Ferris (Pres. Of United Airlines), 4-verso
    - Mr. Edward E. Carlson, Chman and Chief Exec. Officer of UAL Inc (on left) and Robert D. Stuart, Jr., Chman and Chief Exec Officer - Quaker Oats Co., 5
    - Verso: Mr. Edward E. Carlson, Chman and Chief Exec. Officer of UAL Inc (on left) and Robert D. Stuart, Jr., Chman and Chief Exec Officer - Quaker Oats Co., 5-verso
  - Subject files: Los Angeles luncheon, undated; 20 (Box 1549)
    - [Lowell Thomas holding an award at the Los Angeles luncheon], 1
    - [People sitting at banquet tables at the Los Angeles luncheon], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two men at the Los Angeles luncheon], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men at the Los Angelses luncheon], 4
    - [Lowell Thomaswith other men holding an award at the Los Angeles luncheon], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas being presented with an award at the Los Angeles luncheon], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas being presented with an award at the Los Angeles luncheon], 7
  - Subject files: Lynch, Kentucky [M. J. Carroll, Manager's Representative of the U. S. Coal & Coke Company, and E. H. Hollingsworth, Chairman, Employees Committee, 1934; 21 (Box 1549)
    - [M.J. Carroll and E.H. Hollingsworth looking at a book], 1
    - [M.J. Carroll and E.H. Hollingsworth], 2
    - [M.J. Carroll and E.H. Hollingsworth], 3
  - Subject files: Lynch, Kentucky (Lowell Thomas visit), 1934; 22 (Box 1549)
    - [Lowell Thomas with a crowd of people in Lynch, Kentucky], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas visiting Lynch, Kentucky], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a crowd in Lynch, Kentucky], 3
    - [House in Lynch, Kentucky], 4
    - [A house with a garden in Lynch, Kentucky], 5
    - [House with a garden in Lynch, Kentucky], 6
    - [Neighborhood in Lynch, Kentucky], 7
  - Subject files: General MacArthur, undated; 23 (Box 1549)
    - [General MacArthur and Barry Ferris], 1
    - Note [June 23, 1981; Dear I wonder if someone in Barry Ferris' family would like to have this picture where he is with General MacArthur? Sincerely, Lowell Thomas.], 2
    - Note [Sent to the person now head of King Features. Kind Features Syndicate. Joseph F. Delangelo, General Manager 235 E. 45 Street New York, N.Y.], 3
  - Subject files: Jean MacArthur, circa 1970s; 24 (Box 1549)
    - [Lowell Thomas delivering a speech], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas giving a speech], 2
  - Subject files: Machu Picchu, early 1970s; 25 (Box 1549)
    - [Lowell Thomas at Machu Picchu], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and others at Machu Picchu], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas leaning on a rock at Machu Picchu], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas gesturing to a man drinking from a stream at Machu Picchu], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and other at a site in Machu Picchu], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas at Machu Picchu], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at Machu Picchu], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas at the ruins of Machu Picchu], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on ruins at Machu Picchu], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at a llama (?) at Machu Picchu], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas looking down a mountain at Machu Picchu], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting on the ruins at Machu Picchu], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at the base of stairs at the ruins of Machu Picchu], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at the ruins of Machu Picchu], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas looking out at the valley in Macu Picchu], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas at the ruins of Machu Picchu], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas at the ruins of Machu Picchu], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of a mountain at Machu Picchu], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man walking down a hill at Machu Picchu], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas and others looking at a rock at Machu Picchu], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man walking by the ruins at Machu Picchu], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of ruins at Machu Picchu], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas at Machu Picchu], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas at the ruins of Machu Picchu], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in a doorway at Machu Picchu], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and others walking up stairs at Machu Picchu], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of the ruins at Machu Picchu], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas at Machu Picchu], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at ruins at Machu Picchu, 29
  - Subject files: Donald and Claire MacKinnon [color photographs], 1973; 26 (Box 1549)
    - [Donald and Claire MacKinnon], 1
    - Verso [Donald and Claire in pool garden. Jan 1973. All three bedrooms overlook pool garden. A larger garden surrounds all of the house, 1-verso
    - [Claire MacKinnon and her dogs sitting by her pool], 2
    - Verso [Pool garden Oct. 1972.(?) "Peka" "Cindy". Dressing rooms and (?) in background.], 2-verso
    - [Sitting room with pool in the background], 3
    - Verso [(?) pool garden showing dressing rooms (?) trellis walk], 3-verso
    - [People standing on the patio], 4
    - Verso [Terrace of Dame Mabel's beach home at Mr. (?) 1972. A charming home and lovely garden with (?)], 4-verso
    - [The sun shining through a tree], 5
    - Verso [One of my "art" studies. "My star of life." A 6 a.m. sunrise at front of house. "Mooraming (?)" 1973], 5-verso
    - [Dogs outside of a house], 6
    - Verso [Our 2 bedroom windows. One of out 2 (?) windows dressing room. (?) beautiful sheepdog "Bounce and Cindy and Peka"], 6-verso
    - [A group of people gathered on the porch], 7
    - Verso [At Dame Mables summer (beach) home at Mt. Eliza-1972. On the veranda. Mrs. Margarie (?) Watt, Dame Mabel Brookes, Madame Storcesco (?) an old friend, Mrs. Louis Nelken (?)], 7-verso
    - [Kids playing with dogs in front of the pool], 8
    - Verso [Some of the children on our property. All learned to (?) her-My two poodles "Cindy" "Peka" Jan 1973.], 8-verso
  - Subject files: Donald B. MacMillan and Lowell Thomas, 1938, circa 1950s; 27 (Box 1549)
    - Richard Hallet, author, Lowell Thomas, and Commander Donald B. MacMillan, viewing Thomas's catch of fish in Maine; 1938, 1
    - Verso: Richard Hallet, author, Lowell Thomas, and Commander Donald B. MacMillan, viewing Thomas's catch of fish in Maine; 1938, 1-verso
    - [A large crowd gathered around Lowell Thomas], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas holding up an award], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas giving a speech in front of a library], 4
    - Two sailboats in the water], 5
  - Subject files: Main Top (Quaker Hill, Pawling, New York) [color photograph], undated; 28 (Box 1549)
    - [House on Quaker Hill, Pawling, New York], 1
  - Subject files: Maine Lumberjacks, circa 1930s; 29 (Box 1549)
    - Note: Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 1
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 2
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 3
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 4
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 5
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 6
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 7
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 8
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 9
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 10
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 11
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 12
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 13
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 14
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 15
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 16
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 17
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 18
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 19
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 20
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 21
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 22
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 23
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 24
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 25
    - Group from Maine; musicians hired by LT to do performances in and around Pawling, 26
  - Subject files: Marco Polo painting [includes color photographs], circa 1960s - 1970s; 30 (Box 1549)
    - In Marco Polo Club - in Marco Polo room at the Waldorf; LT commissioned painting, 1
    - Note: In Marco Polo Club - in Marco Polo room at the Waldorf; LT commissioned painting, 2
    - In Marco Polo Club - in Marco Polo room at the Waldorf; LT commissioned painting, 3
    - In Marco Polo Club - in Marco Polo room at the Waldorf; LT commissioned painting, 4
    - In Marco Polo Club - in Marco Polo room at the Waldorf; LT commissioned painting, 5
  - Subject files: Marist College Commencement [includes color photographs], 1981; 31 (Box 1549)
    - Lowell Thomas was Marist's commencement speaker in 1981. He is shown here receiving an honorary degree from Dennis Murray (left) and trustee H. Clifton Wilson, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas was Marist's commencement speaker in 1981. He is shown here receiving an honorary degree from Dennis Murray (left) and trustee H. Clifton Wilson, 1-verso
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 2
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 3
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 4
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 5
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 6
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 7
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 8
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 9
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 10
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 11
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 12
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 13
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 14
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 15
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 16
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 17
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 18
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 19
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 20
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 21
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 22
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 23
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 24
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 25
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 26
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 27
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 28
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 29
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 30
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 31
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 32
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 33
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 34
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 35
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 36
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 37
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 38
    - [from Marist College Commencement], 39
  - Subject files: Jack McDonnell, undated; 32 (Box 1549)
    - Jack McDonnell, 1
    - Verso: Jack McDonnell, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Martin B. McKneally and George L. Robinson, 1970; 33 (Box 1549)
    - Caption: To Lowell Thomas with appriciation for his years of service to the American public and best wishes from Martin B. McKneally and his friend George Robinson. Aug 14th 1970, 1
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from NY Congressman Martin B. McKneally (R) concerning photograph with George L. Robinson], 2
  - Subject files: Medal of Freedom, 1977 January 10; 34 (Box 1549)
    - Note: Telegram concerning Medal of Freedom ceremony, 1
    - Note: Telegram concerning Medal of Freedom ceremony, 2
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 3
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 4
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 5
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 6
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 7
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 8
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 9
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 10
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 11
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 12
    - Verso: Recipients of Medal of Freedom in Wash., 12-verso
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 13
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 14
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 15
    - Recipients of Medal of Freedom from President Ford in Washington, 16
  Box 1550
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject: James Michener and Lowell Thomas, undated; 1 (Box 1550)
    - [James Michener and Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Subject files: Pictures of John Mulholland, undated; 2 (Box 1550)
    - Husam Bakhsh of Cawnpore, trading magic with John Mulholland - the ring on the cane - M. learning an old East Indian version; Photo by Irene Mulholland, 1
    - Verso: Husam Bakhsh of Cawnpore, trading magic with John Mulholland - the ring on the cane - M. learning an old East Indian version; Photo by Irene Mulholland, 1-verso
    - [photograph of man pulling rabbit out of hat], 2
  - Subject files: Jane Murphy (Sea Education Association), 1976; 3 (Box 1550)
    - [Sailboat going by an iceburg; Jane Murphy, Sea Education Association], 1
    - [Sailboat; Jane Murphy, Sea Education Association], 2
  - Subject files: Ken Nagle, undated; 4 (Box 1550)
    - Caption: Best Wishes Lowell, I enjoyed the [?], Ken Nagle, 1
  - Subject files: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1971; 5 (Box 1550)
    - Manned Spacecraft Center, Houston, Texas Apollo 15 Eva----Astronaut James B. Irwin, lunar module pilot, works at the Lunar Roving vehicle during the first Apollo 15 lunar surface extravehicular activity (EVA-1) at the Headley-Apennie landing site. The shadow of the Lunar Module "Falcon" is in the foreground. This view is looking northeast, with Mount Hadley in the background. This photograph was taken by Astronaut David R. Scott, commander, 1